PRIVACY POLICY FOR TOTAL TECHNOLOGY
===================================

Last Updated 7/17/2021

At Total Technology, accessible from www.totaltechnology.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Total Technology and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Total Technology. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**CONSENT**

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.

When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFO**

We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

* Provide, operate, and maintain our website
* Improve, personalize, and expand our website
* Understand and analyze how you use our website
* Develop new products, services, features, and functionality
* Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes
* Send you emails
* Find and prevent fraud

**LOG FILES**

Total Technology follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Like any other website, Total Technology uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information.

For more general information on cookies, please read ["What Are Cookies".](https://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies/)

**ADVERTISING PARTNERS PRIVACY POLICIES**

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Total Technology.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Total Technology, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Total Technology has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**THIRD PARTY PRIVACY POLICIES**

Total Technology's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**CCPA PRIVACY RIGHTS (DO NOT SELL MY PERSONAL INFORMATION)**

Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:

* Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.
* Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.
* Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

**GDPR DATA PROTECTION RIGHTS**

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

* The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.
* The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.
* The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
* The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
* The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
* The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

**CHILDREN'S INFORMATION**

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Total Technology does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Contact Form

"\*" indicates required fields

First name\*

Last name\*

Email\*

Phone\*

Message

Consent\*

 I agree to the [privacy policy](https://totaltechnology.com/privacy-policy/).

CAPTCHA

Comments

This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

###### Headquarters

295 Hill Dr.  
San Marcos, CA 92078  
888-952-0011  

###### Regional Offices

New York, Michigan, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, and Texas

###### Keep up with our updates on Linkedin

[

](https://www.linkedin.com/company/18451591)

Copyright © 2024 Total Technology. All Rights Reserved. Developed by [TinyFrog Technologies](https://tinyfrog.com/).

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. Accept All Reject All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

SAVE & ACCEPT
